Audumbar Patil

+91 7276793414 audumbar.patil17@vit. Katraj, PUNE.

MERN STACK DEVELOPER WITH ATMOST CYBER SECURITY

A MERN stack developer and VAPT engineer with 1 year of experience in building strong, dependable and interactive platforms and web applications with professional expertise in penetration testing and vulnerability assessments on various applications in different domains. A team player with broad knowledge in securing SDLC and source code analysis to implement security solutions.

KEY COMPETENCIES

- •Vulnerability Assessments and Penetration Testing (VAPT)
- SOC Engineering
- •Web Development (MERN
- Stack)

- •Backend Engineering
- •Web Vulnerability reduction
- Recommendation Engines
- Password Hash Cracking
- Hardware and Software troubleshooting
- •HTML-CSS, JAVA, Python
- •JS (React, Node, Angular)
- Databases (MySQL, MariaDB, MongoDB)
- Wire Shark and network IDS
- •WPA, WPA2, WEP

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Digifuse, IN

Business Development Executive

Jun 2021 - Aug 2021t

Collaborated with the engineering team at Ghorpadi Diesel Loco Shed, Pune to study, analyze and report about various tools, components and machinery involved in locomotives. Managed and studied various case files in the implementation, durability and life cycles of various locomotives using in the Indian Railways.

Indian Railways Ghorpadi Locoshed Engineering Trainee

Jan 2022 - Aug 2023

Lead market research and presented findings to senior marketing, development and operations team which resulted in an increase of 45% downloads. Managed customer partnerships for the company to help identify pain points and where the company fit in new implementations. Spearhead an incremental user base by 24% through personal SOPs, marketing strategies and implemented reward programs for onboarded users to increase retention.

Oasis InfoBytes Dec 2023 - Present

Website Design and Development

This internship includes few tasks that will help for the basics of HTML CSS and JavaScript. There are total three tasks and each task has few sub tasks. It includes making a landing page, a portfolio website for self, etc. The main task of this internship is to use frontend skills to make a PIZZA DELIVERY app. This pizza delivery app will have all the menu and necessary details to order a pizza.

Unified Mentors

Website Developer Dec 2023 - Present

In this internship the task is to develop two systems using MERN stack. This internship is a full stack internship. A. E Panchayat System: This system will have all the necessary details of bookings and availing services from a gram panchayat office for the villagers. B. EV Charging Slot Booking App: This app will help the EV users to book slot in prior rather than waiting in big queues.

GITHUB:- https://github.com/Audumbar-Patil

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

P.G. Diploma in Computer Science

Swansea University, United Kingdom

Bachelor's Of Technology

Electronics and Telecommunication

Vishwakarma Institute of Technology, PUNE

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Served as the Chief of
- Execution and Secretary at Social Welfare and Development, VIT Pune.
- •Member of National Service Scheme (NSS).
- Volunteered at the Catrina Foundation, head of VIT Socials and volunteer at Sinhagad Animal Welfare and Rescue.
- Head of Aatmabodh (Digital Literacy Program for Senior Citizens and Homemakers).